Oh, I'm sorry, sir.
Yes.
You idiot.
Hurry up and find him.
We don't have much time.
Hurry up.
I'm sorry, sir.
You idiot.
You know, reporter Jung.
Yes.
There's a problem between the company and the company.
What should I do?
I think you should do some more work.
Good luck.
Yes.
Look, reporter Jung.
Did you see the article?
Yes, sir.
You're sitting in the office with a special edict?
It's because of the article.
I don't want to hear it.
Hurry up.
Yes, sir.
Run, run.
Don't think about coming into the office before you get the special edict.
Yes, sir.
Oh, really?
Hey, it's boring.
What kind of cap is that?
Hurry up.
Hey, let's go.
Let's go.
From now on, we're going to fight.
Okay.
Let's go.
Hey.
Come on.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
Hey, let's go.
Let's go.
Can't you guys stop fighting?
What are you doing?
Class three of the fifth grade.
I was really disappointed in you guys.
Is it an arrogant act to choose the class representative?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Mira.
I'm sorry, too.
Don't copy me.
You guys are really ungrateful kids.
Mira.
Now that I think about it, Mira is our class representative.
I'm going to follow you.
Now, let's make up.
Here.
Aren't we good friends?
When I grow up, I want to be one of you guys.
What?
Is that true?
So, I want you guys to work hard as a man.
Don't be cowardly.
Don't be violent.
Hey, Mira.
Can we talk while eating this?
You pig.
If you don't want to eat it...
I'm not a pig.
You guys again?
Promise me.
You'll be a good friend.
Then eat it.
Oh, my.
You guys are really...
Hey!
I want to eat first.
Eat more.
Okay.
You can do it like this.
See?
If we give each other half of it, there's no problem.
Oh, you're back from school.
Hello.
Welcome.
Now that I think about it, Mira and Mira are really good friends.
Where's mom?
Oh, right.
You should study hard.
What's going on?
Our future relatives are here.
Oh, mom, too.
What are you doing?
Our future relatives are here.
You should at least give them some snacks.
What are you doing?
Snacks?
I won't eat it.
Hey!
Wake up.
You're going to go into the girl's house without any manners?
I'm sorry for being rude to you.
My nickname is pig.
What?
You're a pig?
Oh, stop it.
I have class tomorrow.
I'll prepare a lot of food.
Please take good care of Mira.
Okay.
Good-bye.
How did you get caught by Mira already?
A man should have a face.
They're all doing it for you.
No, I was just kidding.
It's late. Let's go.
Listen up.
This isn't a house for kids.
From this moment on,
you guys are like soldiers going to war.
If you disobey orders or leave Ancheong-dong,
I'll give you special training.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Look at their answers.
Everyone, say it out loud.
Do you understand?
Yes.
I'm going to organize it from now on.
If you disobey orders, three people will gather.
Disobey orders!
Stop.
You two, get up.
Look at them.
Who sleeps in one room with a man and a woman?
Yes.
My father sleeps in one room with a woman.
Who sleeps in one room?
My uncle and uncle sleep in one room.
I'm going to go to the campsite
from now on to cheer you up.
Everyone, go!
It's all because of you.
Who slept next to Mi-ra?
What?
So what?
Do you want to fight?
Hey, hey!
No, no.
Don't do anything stupid.
Yes.
Get yourself together by the time you get to the camp.
San Gyeol.
Actually, I'm like that too.
My back is sore.
Shall we sit on our backs?
Yes.
Let's sit on our backs.
Hyuk!
No!
Why are you screaming? It's scary.
Did you hear that?
I don't know.
I don't like it.
You almost got me.
Why are you so scared?
Look over there.
Where?
There's a light in the forest.
You're lying.
Really?
Yes.
Let's go.
Mi-ra!
Don't go!
Don't come if you're scared.
I'll go check.
No, I'm scared.
She's a woman.
What's that?
Over there.
What?
Let's go.
But the goblin...
Where's the goblin?
Mi-ra, let's not go.
Don't come if you're scared.
I'm not scared!
What if we get lost?
You fool.
You might not find the right way.
Follow me.
Anyway, let's go south.
Let's give up and go back.
I'm scared.
Do you know the way back?
Can't we just go back?
Stop laughing and follow me.
Hurry.
Fools.
It's night birds.
Night birds?
Follow me.
Be careful.
Go down.
Where are we?
What's that sound?
Look over there.
There's a cave.
Where?
Let's go in there.
What if there's a bear?
It's better than staying here.
Let's go in the cave.
Let's go.
Wait!
I have a flashlight.
Turn it on.
It's a huge cave.
Okay.
Let's go inside.
No, I'm scared.
Hold my hand.
Go ahead.
Okay.
Let's go.
It's blocked.
We can't go in.
Let's find another way.
Let's go that way.
Let's go.
Look over there.
Who are you?
My name is Lukas.
I'm from Aria, 80,000 light years away.
An alien?
But why do you live in such a dark and scary cave?
I was a scientist in Aria.
But I fell in love with Joanna, who started my research.
I fell in love with her.
I was sent to Aria.
It was already 999 years ago.
What?
999 years?
That's right.
Now my research is at the final stage.
If I complete the first-person view of this Aria,
I can go back to Aria.
But my body is running out of energy.
So I went out to find energy.
To you guys.
The goblin from before?
That's right.
I'm dizzy.
Sir, please send us back.
Then we'll help you as much as we can.
I'd like to do that, too.
But the strong electromagnetic waves from my body
will be transmitted to you.
It's dangerous for Joanna to see you.
Then what should we do?
Is there any other way?
There's only one way.
Before you get exposed to Joanna,
if you can find the energy charge material...
I'll try.
If you can find that material,
I'll give you the energy of a powerful super-missile.
What's that material?
I don't know what kind of material on Earth
can release that energy.
I don't know.
You guys have to find it.
Then follow that light.
What happened?
Nothing.
Really?
Mira.
I'm sorry.
You waited a long time, didn't you?
I was late to dress up nicely.
Thank you for inviting me.
Thank you.
You're so reliable.
You protected Mira as you promised.
So let's have a good time today.
No.
Mira was braver.
That's right.
We're safe because of her.
What do you mean?
We're meeting aliens.
Are you dreaming?
It means you protected us.
Right?
Yes.
How can you be so kind?
You're so sweet.
I hope we can be friends from now on.
Me too.
What's wrong?
It's dad.
Dad, come here.
Mira, I bought you a birthday gift.
I have a lot of friends.
You're late.
Did you catch the electromagnetic waves?
Yes.
Over there.
The electromagnetic waves are strong.
He must be in here.
Let's go.
That's Lucas' invention.
It's an electromagnetic energy release device.
Go find him.
Yes.
He's dead now.
The electromagnetic energy release device is in our hands.
The electromagnetic waves are strong.
You can't see him.
He couldn't have gone far.
We have to catch him.
What's going on?
Let go of me.
What are you doing?
Let's go.
Hurry up.
Calm down.
Mira.
Don't stop me.
Honey.
What's going on?
Mira is dead.
Did you hurt her?
She's in a coma.
How is she?
I'm doing my best, but I don't know.
Then...
Calm down.
Please help me, Maria.
Please help my friend, Mira,
who is the kindest and prettiest person in the world.
Please help me, Maria.
Please help my friend, Mira.
If only we could find our friend, Mira,
we would be punished for her.
I have a good idea.
What is it?
Lucas.
That's right.
If Lucas is super-powerful,
let's take Mira to him.
But we can't find him.
We can't find him.
We can't find him now.
We can find him later.
That's true.
But how can we find Mira?
Leave it to me.
Why are you sleeping like that?
Honey.
Mira is gone.
She's gone.
Honey, call the police.
Call the police.
Lucas.
Mira.
I'm sorry, father.
I'm sorry.
No.
It's my fault.
I'm sorry.
Be quiet.
Have you found Gwang-seok?
Lucas.
Mira.
Please help me.
No.
Jo Hanna is here right now.
Do the adults break their promise in Ariel?
Please help me.
Please.
If it's for Lucas,
I'll do anything.
There's one way.
What is it?
If I can save Mira,
I'll do anything.
Yes.
The mysterious star of the galaxy,
the mysterious energy of the three elements.
Then you'll have super-power.
If you have super-power,
you can save Mira.
Thank you, Lucas.
If you get the energy of the three elements,
you'll become the space warrior Sigma
Then you'll have a duty
to replace the evil in the universe.
I will.
Do you know how dangerous the fight against the evil is?
If you don't do it well, even your life...
We can do it.
We can do it for our friend Mira.
Your friendship looks really good.
Even if I lose all my energy,
I'll help you.
We'll help you recover Lucas's energy.
Yes.
Good.
Then go and get Mira.
Yes.
Aurora's mystery,
the light of the universe,
the mysterious energy of the three elements.
Now we'll help Lucas.
Lucas is an ordinary earthling now,
so we should give him a name.
Right.
What should we name him?
Oh!
Choo!
It's not Choo!
No.
He lived in a cave in 1999.
How about Gompang?
Gompang?
Gompang!
Gompang, come in.
Good, good.
A huge amount of energy has gathered.
What happened?
I don't know.
This is the energy of the three elements
that Lucas brought with him
Then he didn't leave this place.
You fool.
You've done something new.
Go and find him now.
We don't have time.
Yes.
Mira?
It's really you, isn't it?
Yes, dad. It's me, Mira.
Really?
Honey!
Honey, it's me, Mira.
Mira.
Dad, it's me.
Dad, let me introduce you.
He's the one who saved me.
Minamishul.
This is him?
Then...
You fool.
Dad,
I hope Mr. Gompang lives in our house.
Yes.
Wow!
Isn't it nice?
Honey!
Thank you.
For saving our Mira.
It means it's nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
What's wrong with him?
You should come inside.
It's cold. What's with the clothes?
I don't know if he has any clothes.
Follow me.
Let's go inside.
Yes.
It's nice.
It's so pretty.
It's your mom's clothes.
What's wrong with your clothes?
You don't have any clothes.
I know.
Follow me.
Let go of me.
For our new family,
we're going to have a baby.
Have a good time.
I'm happy to live in this house.
What does that mean?
Auntie,
I hope you feel the same way.
Right?
It's fun, isn't it?
Yes.
Let's put it here.
Thank you.
It's so nice.
It's so pretty.
It's so cool.
It's nice.
Look over there.
What's that arrow in front of us?
Gumpang.
Mister,
we'll help you get your energy back
so that you can go back to your hometown.
Thank you.
Mister,
cheer up.
Are you okay?
You're the best.
Isn't this the land?
No.
It's so cool.
Are you filming a movie?
No, something's wrong.
what are you doing?
Auntie,
are you okay?
Let's get him.
Gangdo.
You bad person.
Why did you hit my uncle?
Stop.
Get him.
I'll kill you.
You bad person.
You can't shoot.
There's nothing like this.
I'll kill you.
You bastard.
You're making a fool of me.
Wait a minute.
You bastard.
Stop.
Gumpang.
Hye-ran.
Say hello.
This is Mr. Lee Jung-sik.
Nice to meet you.
Hye-ran,
you're not kidding, are you?
Why?
He really caught Gangdo.
That's enough.
Let's get to work.
Nice to meet you.
What kind of person is this?
I'm saying nice to meet you.
That's right.
That's enough.
Please pose.
Nice pose.
What's wrong?
You seem to be allergic to the camera.
Nice pose.
One more time.
Please pose.
No, it's okay.
Let's see each other for a moment.
What's wrong with you?
Just for a moment.
Let's see each other.
Lunch will be served soon.
I'll be right back.
Hello, my friend.
My name is Taekwondo Team 3.
Do you want to see it?
Hey, you!
You!
What about you, Jung-sik?
I suddenly got hungry,
so I went to buy some medicine.
Is that so?
Enjoy your meal.
Then let's eat first.
I'm sorry.
Oh, my goodness.
Gompang, you're really a busybody.
What do you mean?
You didn't tell me where your hometown is,
who your family is,
or anything else.
I'll tell you everything later.
Do you have any secrets?
What do you mean secrets?
Do you know?
Do you have a lover in your hometown?
What are you talking about?
This earth...
No, no, no.
The whole universe.
I only know one person.
Oh, my goodness.
Who is that?
It's Hera.
Oh, my goodness.
Hera.
What?
Hera, run!
Oh, my goodness.
Gompang.
Sit down!
Sit down, please.
Where did he go?
He's gone.
Thank you.
We're friends.
You idiot.
Did you know where your hometown is?
I even know where my family is.
Okay.
Stand in front of me.
This is my house.
Get him!
Nice to meet you.
You're going all the way?
Get him!
I can't let you go until you're happy.
Go far away.
What about Hera?
I can't.
Where should I go now?
Oh, my goodness.
You idiot.
I'll kill you.
I don't think he'll come.
Why?
Did we do something wrong?
No.
I don't want our family to be a mess because of you.
The weather is so cold.
I told you to keep an eye on him.
He's not here.
What did you say?
I have a good idea.
What is it?
I'll give you a bait.
A bait?
I believe in the earthling who used to live with Lucas.
That's a good idea.
Get ready.
Bye.
Taxi.
Are you going to Shinmun-ro?
No.
Okay.
Taxi.
It's no use trying to fool us.
Hello?
We're protecting your sister Hera.
If you don't give us the mold by 12 o'clock tomorrow,
then...
Are you kidnapping me?
Hera.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
The mold.
You found Hera, didn't you?
I did everything I could to find her.
Why?
Hera went missing last night.
What?
Hera! Hera!
My back!
Look at me!
What happened to Hera?
She was kidnapped.
Who did it?
I don't know.
The mold wanted to find Hera.
So I was on my way to Shinmun-ro to find her.
Where is it?
It's a cave under Yongdu Mountain.
If the mold doesn't come by 12 o'clock tomorrow,
Hera will be...
Okay.
Leave everything to me.
Guys!
We're in trouble!
What's wrong, Mira?
What's going on?
We're in trouble!
The mold went to see Johanna!
What?
Then we should go!
Johanna!
I made the promise!
I'm Lucas!
Untie Hera!
You still don't have the courage to change.
Hera!
The mold!
You like meat, don't you?
Red blood and blue blood.
Hot love.
Untie Hera as you promised.
Untie her?
Okay, I'll untie her.
Please!
Johanna!
Kongpang!
You're a good person.
Are you okay?
I'm okay, Hera.
Take him away!
Hera!
Stop!
Kongpang!
Get rid of them!
No!
Let's get together!
It's cold.
Let's wait and see.
Hera!
Let's go!
Mister!
Hera!
Wake up!
Kongpang!
Get up!
It's you guys.
Look!
The aliens ran away.
If we save Gwangsang, we can go back to Asia.
Thank you.
If you weren't so brave.
Don't mention it.
Hera!
If we save Gwangsang, can you go back to Asia with me?
I don't know.